idealshape.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Welcome to IdealShape, LLC and Meine and Associates, LLC. IdealShape has created the following privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to protecting your privacy, and to disclose our information-gathering and dissemination practices. This online privacy policy is here to tell you about, among other things, the information IdealShape collects through our Web site, how we use that information, how you can opt out of certain uses of the information we collect, and how IdealShape can make changes to this privacy policy. Please let us know if you have any questions regarding this privacy policy by contacting us at [privacy@IdealShape.com](mailto:privacy@beachbody.com).

**A note about children’s privacy…**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have inadvertently obtained personal information on a child under the age of 13, that information will be deleted from our systems. IdealShape encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child’s online experience safer:

  * Teach kids never to give out personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. This includes their name, address, phone, school, etc.
  * Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.
  * Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child’s information is being treated.

**What information does IdealShape collect?**

In collecting your personal information, we aim to provide you with a more customized experience. This information lets us provide services and features that we think are more likely to meet your needs. Of course, users can browse our Web site without providing any personal information, but once you give us this personal information, you are not anonymous to us.

IdealShape collects two types of information when you visit our Web site: information that may be used to identify you individually, such as your name and email address (“personal information”), and non-personal information, such as IP addresses, the type of browser you are using, and aggregated information about user activities on our Web site (“non-personal information”).

**Personal Information:** We specifically request personal information from you at certain points on our Web site. For example, when you sign up for our newsletter, subscribe to our Web site, or when you purchase an item through our Web site, we collect personal information to complete the transaction. This information may include, without limitation, your name, shipping and billing addresses, telephone number, email address, and credit card information. If you apply to join our Affiliate Program, we may collect information about your business, including, without limitation, your (or your organization’s) name, email address, street address, telephone number, tax identification number, and information about your Web site (e.g., the URL, the number of unique users and page views, the demographics of your user base, etc.). From time to time, we may also request personal information about you and your interests in surveys, contest entry forms, or in other ways. You may always choose not to provide us with your personal information; however, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific product or service, or to offer you personalized content.

**Non-Personal Information:** When you visit our Web site, we also collect non-personal information, such as your IP address, which is a number that can be used to identify your location and Internet Service Provider. We may also collect the URL from which you came to our Web site and the URLs visited on our Web site. A URL is the full address of a Web site page, which may contain some personal or identifying information about the person who is viewing it.

**Use of Cookies:** We also use a feature of your browser called a cookie to assign identification to your computer. The unique user ID contained within your cookie automatically identifies your computer—but not you—to our servers every time you visit our Web site. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user, but may be correlated with identity information in our log files. You can turn off the cookie feature by using your browser preference options, but you may not be able to utilize some services properly. Current versions of many Web browsers offer enhanced user controls for the placement and duration of cookies. Search for “cookies” under your Web browser’s Help menu for more information on the cookie management features available to you.

**Use of Pixel Tags:** We also collect information through the use of “pixel tags” included in email messages we may send to you. Pixel tags are tiny graphic files, not visible to the human eye, that are included in HTML-encoded email messages. When such a message is opened in an HTML-capable email program, the recipient’s computer will access our server to retrieve the pixel tag file, allowing us to record and store, along with the recipient’s email address, the date and time the recipient viewed the email message, the fact that the recipient’s email program is capable of receiving HTML-encoded email, and other standard logging information. The pixel tag also may see or read cookies.

**How does IdealShape use or disclose the information it collects?**

IdealShape’s Use of Personal Information and Non-Personal Information: We use your personal information to process your requests, to improve the features of our Web site, and to communicate with you. We may also use your personal information to personalize our Web site, to target advertising or promotions that may be of interest to you, and to analyze aggregate user data in order to improve our services. On occasion, we may also contact you about IdealShape or Product Partners’ products or services that we think you will find useful. We might also contact you to see if you are interested in participating in market research regarding IdealShape. For information about opting out of such communications, please see our Opt-Out Policy section below.

**Co-Branded Offers:** In arranging to have marketing and promotional information of certain companies or businesses with whom IdealShape or Product Partners may have formed a strategic alliance (“Affiliated Companies”), we may disclose to the Affiliated Companies your personal information, including information such as your shipping address, name, and contact information. If you do not want to us to disclose your personal information to the Affiliated Companies, please refer to the Opt-Out Policy below.

**Cookies (again):** We may use cookie and IP address information to count and track Web site visits in the aggregate, to personalize the Web site for each unique user, to control the frequency of individual advertisements to individual computers, and to target advertisements and promotions to broad demographic segments. We may also use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site.

**Customer Service Issues and Contacts:** We may use your email address to contact you in response to customer service complaints you have submitted, to address a problem affecting your use of the service, or to verify information concerning a transaction.

**Transaction Processing:** When you make a purchase on our Web site, we may need to provide personal information, including information such as your shipping address, billing information, telephone number, and credit card information, to third parties, including product manufacturers and shipping companies, as necessary solely to complete the transaction.

**Legal Requirements:** We may disclose personal information when we deem necessary or appropriate to law enforcement or other entities or third parties as required by law or to protect our rights or the rights of others, to prevent harm to persons or property, to fight fraud, identity theft, or otherwise to comply with the law or legal process, to respond to claims, to protect our systems and customers, to ensure the integrity and operation of our business and systems, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of IdealShape and its employees or others.

**Business and Accounting Disclosures:** We may also disclose non-identifying transaction information to third parties for the purpose of accounting and record keeping. We may also disclose aggregate user data or non-personal information in order to describe our services to prospective business partners, advertisers, and others, but will do so only in a form that does not identify individual users.

**Other Disclosures:** Occasionally we may disclose personal information in other circumstances, but we will only do this if we have explained at the time we collect the information the purpose for which it will be disclosed.

**Opt-Out Policy**

You may opt out of receiving communication from us, from Affiliated Companies, or from other third parties by emailing us at: [privacy@IdealShape.com](mailto:privacy@beachbody.com) or writing to us at:

Meine and Associates, LLC – DBA IdealShape

176 Dry Canyon Drive

Lindon, Utah  84042

Attention: Privacy Policy Department
